He always wanted
the Su family's approval
Just give him an engagement
And he won't fall out with us easily
What Su Yurou holds
The key authorization is more important
As long as she signs the prenup
The cooperation with
the Gu family will be secured
Turn it off
After the wedding find a decent
Excuse to appease her
She's easy to coax
Mr. Gu, what if Miss Su disagrees
She won't disagree
She can't let go of this engagement
That's too harsh
So it wasn't true love
but an arrangement
No wonder he didn't look for me today
Sister
Is there a misunderstanding
about this recording
If it's a misunderstanding
You'll know after listening to it all
I've already backed up the complete file
If needed I can
Hand it to professionals
for authentication
You had this prepared all along
You're the one
who arranged this long ago
Could you please cast my
Phone screen to the big screen
I'll do it